Interceptor drone companies in Ukraine
have figured out how to keep their
pilots out of Harm's way.
We've come to a very secretive site in
Keant
access to a wild hornits training zone.
Now, these are perhaps some of the best
known, most prolific and certainly most
effective of the interceptor drone
manufacturers currently in Ukraine. The
distance between pilot and drone is
usually limited by the radio frequency
of
here in that means the operators are
increasingly.
Тобто неважливо від дистанції, від
умовного кордону, типа з ворогом.
Потрібно постійно слідкування за
маскуванням, тим більше розвитки, тим
більше ударних дронів. Все спрямовується
на екіпажі ППО.
Зараз ми працюємо над тим, щоб можна
було збивати, наприклад, працювати
стінгами з іншого континенту, не тільки
з іншої країни.
able to defend a large part of Ukraine's
airspace,
much needed as Russia steps up its
aerial assault on Ukraine. You can read
more on business.com.
Yeah.